# Carlos López Monreal

Software Engineer

## **Details**

Valencia, Spain (+34) 665 48 58 04 c.lopemonreegmail.com

## Links



in LinkedIn



## Skills

| Java           |  |
|----------------|--|
| SQL            |  |
| HTML           |  |
| CSS            |  |
| JavaScript     |  |
| PHP            |  |
| SASS           |  |
| Angular        |  |
| Bootstrap      |  |
| Spring         |  |
| Git            |  |
| Linux Terminal |  |
| IONIC          |  |

## Languages

Spanish · native English · intermediate

## **Profile**

Firstly, I define myself as a hard-working, committed and curious person, with a great desire to add value to a company. Always willing to learn and live new experiences.

On the other hand, I am constantly learning new technologies and programming tools, in order to putting it into practice, thus improving my portfolio.

## **Employment History**

ATM Software Engineer Oct. 2022 - Jan. 2023

Java Software Development in an international project related with Air Traffic Management (ATM).

GNSS Trainee at GNSS Academy Jan. 2022 - May. 2022

I acquired the necessary knowledge on GNSS thanks to the development of an end-to-end Python project involving Real Data Campaigns, Tools Execution, Signal processing, and Ranging and User Navigation performances.

## Education

Industrial Electronic and Automatic Engineering, Universidad Politécnica de Valencia Sept. 2016 - Jun. 2022

My Final Degree Project was about the improvement in the vertical profile automation of a flight simulator software with Java language.

#### Courses

Desarrollo Web Completo con HTML5, CSS3, JS, PHP y MySQL

Desarrollo Web con Java EE, Spring, JPA e Hibernate

Mar. 2023

Måster en SQL Server

Jan. 2023

Spring Framework 5 & Spring Boot 2 desde cero

Dec. 2022

Curso MondoDB desde cero

Nov. 2022

Curso Apache Kafka desde cero

Docker, de principiante a experto

Nov. 2022

Mayen Crash Course

Oct. 2022

PEARSON TEST OF ENGLISH GENERAL (CEF B2)

Aug. 2022